[
  {
    "question" : "What is your superpower",
    "choices" : ["Flying", "Extreme Luck", "Super Speed", "Super Strength"],
    "answers" : [20, 80, 60, 20]
  },

  {
    "question" : "What is your fruit",
    "choices" : ["Mango", "Blueberry", "Banana", "Apple"],
    "answers" : [20, 80, 60, 40]
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is your tree",
    "choices": ["Oak", "Red Wood", "Birch", "Binary"],
    "answers" : [80, 40, 60, 20]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Do you like school",
    "choices" : ["Yes", "No", "So-So", "Whats school"],
    "answers" : [10 , 60, 30, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Do you like sports",
    "choices" : ["Yes", "No", "So-So", "What are sports"],
    "answers" : [30, 10, 20, 10]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Do you looove spending money",
    "choices" : ["Yes", "No", "money's gone","Whats money"],
    "answers" : [50, 30, 80, 20]
  },
  {
    "question" : "What's your subject",
    "choices" : ["Math", "Art", "History", "Chemistry"],
    "answers" : [10, 80, 50, 30]
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is the animal of choice",
    "choices" : ["Dog", "Cat", "Bird", "Fish"],
    "answers" : [60, 80, 40, 20]
  },
  {
    "question" : "What Streaming Service",
    "choices" : ["Amazon Prime", "Apple TV", "Netflix", "Disney+"],
    "answers" : [20, 40, 60, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "How many pounds of potatoes have you eaten in your life",
    "choices" : ["100", "20", "50", "5"],
    "answers" : [100, 20, 50 ,5]
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is your favorite type of gambling",
    "choices" : ["Sports Betting", "Roulette", "Black Jack", "Scratch Cards"],
    "answers" : [30, 70, 50, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Do you love Clash Royale",
    "choices" : ["yes", "no", "so-so", "whats clash royale"],
    "answers" : [50, 20, 30, 10]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Are you an Alchoholic",
    "choices" : ["yes", "no", "meh", "whats alcohol"],
    "answers" : [60, 30, 80, 10]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Whats your favorite weather",
    "choices" : ["Sunny", "Cloudy", "Rainy", "Windy"],
    "answers" : [20, 40, 70, 50]
  },
  {
    "question" : "MacOS vs WindowsOS vs LinuxOS vs iOS",
    "choices" : ["Mac", "Windows", "Linux", "iOS"],
    "answers" : [30, 50, 10, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "You have a 100% chance to get 1 million dollars or a 50% chance for 100 million or a 25% chance for 1 billion or a 10% chance for 100 billion",
    "choices" : ["100 million", "1 million", "1 billion", "100 billion"],
    "answers" : [30, 0, 50, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Are you good at chess",
    "choices" : ["yes", "no", "so-so", "whats chess"],
    "answers" : [10, 40, 30, 10]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Whats the derivative of arctangent",
    "choices" : ["1/((x^2) + 1))", "-1/sqrt(1-(x^2))", "2x", "tangent"],
    "answers" : [10, 30, 60, 80]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Pick a number 1-4",
    "choices" : ["1", "2", "3","4"],
    "answers" : [100, 0, 0, 0]
  },
  {
    "question" : "Pick a number 1-4 again",
    "choices" : ["1", "2", "3","4"],
    "answers" : [0, 100, 0 ,0]
  }
]